<Publish>
  <ModId Value="92908" />
  <DisplayName Value="Write Everywhere" />
  <ShortDescription Value="Write texts in the CS2 world!" />
  <LongDescription># IT'S BETA AND IT MAY BREAK YOUR GAME. USE AT YOUR OWN RISK!

This is the Cities Skylines 2 version of Write Everywhere ([CS1 mod version here](https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2887458944)). 
It keep some of the features from the CS1 version plus some new features that are only possible in CS2.

For detailed reference and samples, [look this repository](https://github.com/klyte45/CS2-WriteEverywhereFiles).

## Suggested usages

- Add texts in game from properties of any object of the game
- Add textured planes to simulate structures, like walls and signs
- Make color-animated planes with images (requires some coding)
- Add plates to the vehicles of the game with the style you wish.

This list isn't exhaustive and many more uses are already possible. Use your imagination!

## Requirements

This mod is simpler to understand when compared with its CS1 version, but it still being a mod with a lot of stuff that must be discovered by the users - specially at this moment.

More documentation will be added in the future.

## Write Everywhere modules

Very soon the Paradox Mods will start receiving mods that are WE modules. They are designed to add automatically new content into the Write Everywhere, like:

- Image atlases
- Default layouts to assets
- Importable layouts (into City Layouts tab)
- Fonts to be imported

Notice that fonts will always require manual install in the city (by adding them in the City Fonts tab). To make things easier, was added a button to list all mods that registered fonts/layouts in Write Everywhere at file picker dialog.

If you are interested to create your own modules, take a look at [this template repository](https://github.com/klyte45/CS2-WEModuleTemplate).

This feature was heavily inspired by the [Station Entrance Visuals](https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/94028/Windows) by rodrigmatrix. That mod will be set up to follow the new integration method soon.

## FAQ

First of all, read the [files repository](https://github.com/klyte45/CS2-WriteEverywhereFiles) to get the basic information.

- **How I can customize the vehicle plate letters and number?** 
  - It will be available in another mod. [Addresses mod will have a implementation](https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/74182/Windows) in future versions, wait for news.
- **The vehicle plates are not appearing in my game!**
  -  It's probably because you either haven't added the plate locations folder inside your local layouts folder (as explained in the files repository above) or didn't imported a plate layout to your savegame. Notice that not all vehicles were mapped yet.
- **How can I find the properties of the objects to get the texts?**
  - If what you want is not in the builtin functions, so you will need to use modders tools like [Scene Explorer](https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/74285/Windows) to inspect the objects you want to extract information from.
- **There's any Discord server I can ask for help with this mod?**
  - No, I have no specific Discord server for support. Leave your questions at Paradox forums and I will response as soon as I can.
  - You can ask for assistance in general Discord servers from CS2, may I be there but I can't promise I will be able to respond.
- **There are any videos showing how to use this mod?**
  - Not from me. Maybe fellow youtubers/streamers can learn stuff from this mod and make videos in the future (let me know if you do any to highlight here)

## Special thanks
I want to thank the people that helped me with CS2 modding since first days, specially mentioning **yenyang** and **krzychu**. Also thanks **Chameleon**, **Mimonsi** and **Nullpinter** for testing the mod during the development process.</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/write-everywhere-cities-skylines-2-version.1711901/" />
  <ModVersion Value="0.1.1.2" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
  <ChangeLog>#  v0.1.1r2 (07-DEC-24)
- Added feature to setup fonts and atlases for layouts loaded from modules. You can export settings to use in other savegames.
  - It allows to replace any font or atlas used in a layout from prefab loaded from a WE module to an existing one in the game. 
  - As default, fonts from WE modules are all the default until get setup. Atlases from WE modules are the ones setted up in the module.
- Added feature to copy a atlas from a WE module to the local atlases folder - useful for editing them to replace the original
  - Export the atlas, edit them at `exportedAtlases` folder, then move it to `imageAtlases` folder, all relative to WE data folder at AppData
- Fixed: UI Crashing when trying to type the path address at file picker dialog</ChangeLog>
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\0_main.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\0__new_0.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\1_a.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\2_b.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\3_c.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Screenshots\4_d.jpg" />
  <Dependency Id="74417" ModVersion="" DisplayName="Unified Icon Library" />
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/klyte45/CS2-WriteEverywhere" />
  <ExternalLink Type="youtube" Url="https://www.youtube.com/Klyte45" />
  <ExternalLink Type="kofi" Url="https://ko-fi.com/klyte45" />
</Publish>